So friends, finally ICICI LBD has
disclosed its quarter 2 numbers.
In today's meeting, the company has
approved its financial results.  The company has
also announced an interim dividend of
₹6.50, meaning the
company is going to pay a dividend of ₹6.50 on every share you hold.  The
record date related to this is going to be
23 October 2025 and the
payment of this dividend will be made before 12 November
2025, as per the company
's information.  So this was the
information related to corporate action.  Now let's
move on to the company's numbers.
We have come to the actual numbers of the company.
We are seeing all the amount of data
in these lax.  I will
convert it into crores and tell you
friends.  So the total income of the company for this quarter is
seen to be
around Rs 6582 crore.
In the last quarter, the company had generated total income of Rs 683 crore and last year Rs
5850 crore.
So,
we are seeing the total income of the company
growing significantly yearly as well as quarterly.  Let's talk about the
net premium of the company.  So what is the
net premium generated by the company in this quarter,
friends?
5651 crore was generated in the previous quarter
and 5136 crore was
earned as net premium last year.
So, we are seeing the net premium of the company growing significantly yearly and quarterly.
Talking about the
company's expenses, the total expenses of the company for this
quarter are approximately Rs 5 crore
83 lakh.  The company had incurred expenses of Rs 5 crore 42 lakh in the last quarter
and Rs
5 crore 18 lakh last year.
So we are seeing the company's expenses increasing significantly yearly and quarterly.
Talking about operating profit, the
company's operating profit for this quarter
is Rs 752 crore.  In the previous quarter it
was Rs 654 crore and last year the
company had generated an operating profit of Rs 664 crore.
So, we are seeing the operating profit of the company growing significantly yearly and quarterly.
If we talk about net profit, the
net profit of the company for this quarter has been Rs
819 crore.  In the last quarter it
was Rs 747 crore and last year the company had generated a net profit of Rs 693 crore
or around Rs 694 crore.
So,
friends, we are seeing the net profit of the company increasing significantly yearly and quarterly.  And if we
talk about the EPS of the company.
So friends, the company's EPS for this quarter
is ₹16.49.   The
company generated EPS of ₹14.5 in the last quarter and ₹15.6 in the last year.
So, the EPS of the company yearly quarterly
also
appeared to be performing very well.  Friends,
if we talk about NPS, then the company has not disclosed the
net NPS etc. of this quarter
here as of now,
friends, and if it was here then
we would have studied the NPS also.  So
friends, these were the numbers of ICICI LB.  I hope you found the
video informative.  You must have liked it.
If you liked it, please like the video
and subscribe to the channel.
Thank you.